Privacy Policy
==============

We believe you should always know what data we collect from you and how we use it, and that you should have meaningful control over both. We want to empower you to make the best decisions about the information that you share with us. 

That’s the basic purpose of this Privacy Policy.

**You should read this policy in full, but here are a few key things we hope you take away from it:**

Playeur is public and media is immediately viewable and searchable by anyone around the world. We give you non-public ways to communicate on Playeur too, through protected Direct Messages. You can also use Playeur under a pseudonym if you prefer not to use your name.

When you use Playeur, even if you’re just looking at media, we receive some personal information from you like the type of device you’re using and your IP address. You can choose to share additional information with us like your email address, phone number, address book contacts, and a public profile. We use this information for things like keeping your account secure and showing you more relevant videos, people to follow, and ads.

We give you control through your [settings](https://playeur.com/settings) to limit the data we collect from you and how we use it, and to control things like account security, marketing preferences.

In addition to information you share with us, we use your videos you’ve viewed, Liked, or Reposted, and other information to determine what channels you’re interested in, your age, the languages you speak, and other signals to show you more relevant content. We give you transparency into that information, and you can modify or correct it at any time.

If you have questions about this policy, how we collect or process your personal data, or anything else related to our privacy practices, we want to hear from you. You can [contact us](https://help.playeur.com/en/support/tickets/new) at any time.

### Information You Share With Us

We require certain information to provide our services to you. For example, you must have an account in order to upload, share, comment, and vote on Playeur. When you choose to share the information below with us, we collect and use it to operate our services. 

### Basic Account Information

You don’t have to create an account to use some of our service features, such as searching and viewing public Playeur profiles or watching a video. If you do choose to create an account, you must provide us with some personal data so that we can provide our services to you. 

### Public Information

Most activity on Playeur is public, including your profile information, your language when you created your account, and your published media content, and certain information about your published media content like the date, and time. 

### Information We Collect

This is information that you provide us through text fields, such as your name, payment information and benefits. The information we collect differs depending on if you make an account as a content creator, or become a user.

You also have the option to add more information to your public profile, such as a location, social media links, and an about section, which we store along with any comments or messages you submit on Playeur. 

### User provided information

You may provide a variety of information about yourself to us, such as your name, voice and image (in any content you upload), Playeur username, email address, postal mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and billing information when you register for Playeur Services; upload, purchase, view, or download certain content or products from the Playeur Services. 

### Automatically Collected Information

When you access the Playeur Services or open one of our emails, we automatically record and store certain information about your system by using cookies and other types of technologies. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters that are sent to your browser. For information about what cookies are, how they work, how Playeur uses them, and how to remove them, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://playeur.com/terms/). Examples of such information we automatically collect include Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), a unique user ID, device and browser types and identifiers, referring and exit page addresses, software and system type, and information about your usage of Playeur Services. Examples of how Playeur uses automatically collected information include to: (a) automatically update the Playeur application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Playeur Services; (c) provide customized advertisements, content, and information; (d) monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns; (e) monitor and store aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (f) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities.

### Information from Other Sources

We may obtain additional information such as demographic and statistical information from third parties and sources other than the Playeur Services, such as advertisers or social media networks (such as Facebook) for which you have approved our access. When you access the Playeur Services through social media networks or when you connect the Playeur Services to social media networks, you are authorizing Playeur to collect, store, and use such additional information and content in accordance with this Privacy Notice. We use this information to supplement the information we collect about you in order to provide more relevant, safer experiences for you with the Playeur Services and improve the Playeur Services, analytics, and advertising. If we combine or associate information from other sources with information that we collect through the Playeur Services, we will treat the combined information in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

### How Playeur Uses Personal Information

Playeur uses such information to operate, maintain, enhance, provide, create, and develop all of the features, functionality, and services (new or existing) found on the Playeur Services; provide security for our websites, products, software, or applications; manage relationships with Playeur account holders (e.g., Partners, Affiliates), including making or receiving payment; improve users’ experience with Playeur by providing content recommendations and by delivering content that we hope users will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; allow you to comment on content, and participate in online games, contests, or rewards programs; prevent fraud and abuse; and understand the usage trends of our users.

We use your email address and/or telephone number to communicate with you, including to notify you of major Playeur Services updates, for customer service purposes, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Playeur Services. We may still send you additional informational or transactional notifications.

Playeur may periodically send promotional materials or notifications to you related to the Playeur Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can go to your account settings once you have logged in to the Playeur Services or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of any email from us. 

In certain cases, we have a legal obligation to collect and process your personal information (such as our obligation to share data with tax authorities).

We may also ask for your consent to process your personal information for a specific purpose that we communicate to you. When you consent to our processing your personal information for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time and we will stop processing of your data for that purpose.

Playeur will rely on legal grounds to process your personal information to the extent permitted by applicable law, which may include, without limitation: to honor contractual commitments, to take steps in anticipation of entering into contract, to fulfill legal obligations, your consent, and Playeur's legitimate interests.

### When Playeur Discloses Personal Information

We share such information as described below:

We disclose such information to service providers working on our behalf such as to: provide website hosting maintenance and security services conduct data analysis and create reports offer certain functionality or assist Playeur in improving the Playeur Services and creating new services and features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice we authorize them to use the information only for the purposes for which it is provided to them and we require them to use reasonable confidentiality measures.

Playeur may disclose user information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with U.S. state and federal laws or other applicable laws around the world (for example, in the country of your residence) or respond to a court order judicial or other government request subpoena or warrant in the manner legally required.

Playeur also reserves the right to disclose information that we believe in good faith is appropriate or necessary to protect Playeur from potential liability or from fraudulent abusive or unlawful uses investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations protect the security or integrity of the Playeur Services or protect the rights property or safety of Playeur our users or others.

Other than as set out in this Privacy Notice you will receive notice when personal information about you might be shared with third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

### Data Subject Rights and Your Choices

You may decline to share certain information with Playeur, in which case Playeur may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Playeur Services. If you have created a Playeur Services account, depending on the service, you may be able to update your profile information and preferences or disable your account by logging in and going to the settings page – for example, [https://playeur.com](https://playeur.com/). For other requests to review, update, delete, or otherwise limit Playeur's use of information that you have provided directly to Playeur, you may contact [privacy@playeur.com](mailto:privacy@playeur.com). In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify all relevant background. To protect your privacy and security, we may take steps to verify your identity before granting you access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), can exercise certain data subject rights available to them under applicable data protection laws.  We will comply with requests to exercise these rights in accordance with applicable law.  Please note that in some circumstances, we may  need to keep processing your information for certain legitimate interests or to comply with a legal obligation.  If these rights apply to you, they may permit you to request that we:

* Obtain access to or a copy of certain personal information we hold about you
* Prevent the processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes (including any direct marketing processing based on profiling)
* Update personal information that is out of date or incorrect
* Delete certain personal information we hold about you
* Restrict the way that we process and disclose specific personal information about you
* Transfer your personal information to a third-party provider of services
* Revoke consent that you previously provided for the processing of your personal information

For more information on how to exercise these rights.  If applicable, you may make a complaint to the data protection supervisory authority in the country where you are based. Alternatively, you may seek a remedy through local courts if you believe your rights have been breached.

### Account Closure & Deletion

If you would like to close your account and delete your profile information you may update or delete information tied to your account, or close an account, by accessing the “My Account” area of the service or by submitting a help ticket to that service. If you close your account, Playeur may retain certain information about you for the activities described in this Privacy Notice, or as permitted or required by applicable law.

### Third-Party Services and Websites

The Playeur Services may link to third-party websites or services. The privacy practices of those third parties are not governed by this Privacy Notice. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third-party websites and services to understand their practices.

If you connect to a third-party service (such as Facebook, Twitter, or another third-party application) to link your Playeur account with a third-party service, you are requesting and authorizing us to share or grant access to information on your behalf (such as your username, the fact that your connection originated from the Playeur Services, and other relevant usage and diagnostic information) with such third party.

### Advertisers and Analytics Providers

Playeur may use third-party Web analytics services in connection with the Playeur Services. These service providers use a variety of tracking technologies such as cookies to analyze how users use the Playeur Services. The information collected (described above in “Automatically Collected Information”) may be shared with or collected directly by these services and processed to evaluate your use of the Playeur Services.

Playeur may also work with third-party ad networks, advertisers, and  advertising analytics providers to target (and measure the performance of) ads to you both on and off the Playeur Services. We may share with these third parties (or they may directly collect) data such as cookie and mobile ad identifiers in order to engage in advertising activity (including to understand how you respond to advertisements and to serve relevant ads). Playeur also works with third parties to serve ads to you off Playeur's Services. When we do so, we may share information such as your email address or resettable device identifier for that advertising partner to “match” to other information that may have about you.

Advertisers on Playeur, or representatives or service providers working on their behalf (“Playeur Advertisers”), sometimes use technology to serve ads that appear on our services directly to your device. They automatically receive certain data, such as your IP address, when this happens. They may also use cookies (or similar technologies) to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize ad content. This Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we cannot control the tracking technologies and activities of Playeur Advertisers and you should consult their respective privacy policies.

### Global Privacy Control

Global Privacy Control (“**GPC**”) header is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. GPC is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want their personal information to be sold or shared beyond the business with which they intend to interact. Playeur recognizes browser-initiated GPC signals.

### Data Security

Playeur uses a variety of managerial, technical, and physical measures to protect the integrity and security of your information. These measures may vary based on the sensitivity of your information. However, no security precautions or systems can be completely secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Playeur, and you do so at your own risk. We cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

### Retention of Your Information

Playeur maintains data related to your usage of Playeur for as long as it is required in order to fulfill the relevant purposes described in this Privacy Notice, as may be required (or permitted) by law such as for tax and accounting purposes, or as otherwise communicated to you. Once you have asked us to close your account and delete your profile information, we will delete all information that we are not required or permitted to retain by law.

### Children’s Privacy

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS PLAYEUR AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER WITHOUT PARENTAL SUPERVISION. 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Playeur does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information (as defined by the United States Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Playeur learns that personal information of persons under 13 has been collected on or through the Playeur Services, Playeur will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a Playeur Services member, then please contact playeur at [privacy@playeur.com](mailto:privacy@playeur.com) to have that child’s account terminated and personal information deleted.

For residents of the EEA, where processing of personal information is based on consent, Playeur will not knowingly engage in that processing for users under the age of consent established by applicable data protection law. If we learn that we are engaged in that processing with such users, we will halt such processing and will take reasonable measures to promptly remove applicable information from our records.

### Merger or Sale

In the event that Playeur, or some or all assets related to the Playeur Services are acquired by or merged with a third-party entity or in connection with a contemplated change of ownership transaction, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control event, including in the course of diligence.

### International Data Transfers

Information collected by Playeur may be stored and processed in your region, in the United States (for instance in our major data centers), or in any other country where Playeur or its affiliates, subsidiaries, partners, or service providers are located or maintain facilities.  If we provide any information about you to any such entities, we will take appropriate measures to ensure such companies protect your information adequately in accordance with this Privacy Notice and applicable law.

### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice

Playeur reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Notice at any time (for example to reflect updates to the Playeur Services or to reflect changes in the law). Please check this Privacy Notice periodically for those changes. Your continued use of the Playeur Services after the posting of changes constitutes your binding acceptance of such changes.

We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personal information collected in the past under a prior version of the Privacy Notice without the consent of affected individuals.

### Playeur Contact Information

Please contact Playeur with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice at 2810 N Church St, PMB 44417, Wilmington, DE 19802 or by email to [privacy@playeur.com](mailto:privacy@playeur.com). We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt. If you are a California resident, you may have this same information emailed to you by sending a letter to the foregoing address with your email address and a request for this information.

### California Privacy Rights

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (as defined by applicable California law) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of personal information disclosed to those parties. Playeur does not currently disclose personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

##### Product

##### Resources

##### Company

Join the Playeur community!  
The next-generation video platform.
